I still remember it clearly.
It was like something from another world.
The Golden City, where things that are beyond human live.
The place was boundless and vast and overwhelming.
It was beyond anything we could handle.
Sure is hot.
So that rumor about a city of gold at the bottom of the netherworld.
Yeah.
I bet someone saw this and saw it a mail balloon.
What is this?
A building?
Try to be careful, okay?
Sorry.
Look at this, it's some kind of crystal.
Did you hurt yourself?
I'm fine.
And check this out.
It's like it's mixed into the building.
Oh, wow.
Incredible.
How do you think this place was made?
Did the surface collapse and get swallowed up a long time ago?
Did the whole city get turned into a fossil?
Or is it a mirage created by the crystals?
Guess there's no way to be sure.
But it's beautiful.
Yeah.
To be continued...
Must mean we're supposed to blaze our own trail, huh?
In that case, I'll walk in front since I'm able to see the movements of the force field.
You just give us the orders, team leader.
Team leader?
How are your injuries holding up, Greg? Are you able to take the rear?
No problem. Leave it to me.
Come to think of it, all four of us managed to make it down here just fine, didn't we?
Mia!
That would mean White Whistles don't necessarily have to come on their own.
Now that you mention it, that bunch does like to make up their own rules, don't they?
We can just ask the next White Whistle we come across.
You can't be serious. I bet they'd just be another scoundrel.
The sixth layer. The world of the absolute boundary from which no human can return.
A turbinate dragon.
They have terrible poisonous scales that rupture when struck.
And it says that the males fight by aggressively slamming into each other.
They're very tenacious and move freely in three dimensions without any regard to the curse.
Pretty scary.
It says in the sixth layer, one of them is as dangerous as a swarm of amaranthine deceptors.
Nah, pass on that.
Oh, these guys. Must be Mizojacks.
It says they live near geothermals and are calm.
Geothermals? I don't see anything like that here.
Does it say how they taste?
It says their freshly laid eggs are pretty good.
Hey, come here, guys!
I found some eggs!
Oh, they're moving!
Those don't seem like they're very freshly laid.
Well, maybe my mother never ate any just before they started hatching.
You want to try to eat some?
You see that? What is that light?
What's that?
Poison gas! Don't breathe it in!
What is that?
Time to run! Right now, guys!
Hurry!
Were those the geothermals she mentioned?
What a terrible place to make a nest.
They were like huge bubbles, weren't they?
Oh, Riko, why does it sound like you're actually enjoying this?
Ta-da!
Whoa!
They made it through that without breaking?
Sure are strong!
How is it?
Should be fine if we boil it.
I'm so hungry.
Hurry up and open it.
It's still alive even after we boiled it?
I don't know.
Looks dead to me.
Maybe it's just a reflex.
Boiling must not be enough to break down their muscles.
I wonder what sort of body they have.
I would have preferred a freshly laid one.
Are you for real?
You're actually going to try it?
It's moving inside my mouth.
Is it any good?
Can you give it a little flavor?
If you do a good job, Nanachi might do it again.
What the heck?
What do you mean by that?
Riko, no!
I don't want that thing!
Smash this up.
Coat everything.
And then cook it.
It's still moving.
But I admit it does smell really good.
Great.
Pretty good once you get used to it.
Was it too hot?
Uh, so hot.
Huh?
We did it!
Here, just try to slow down a little.
I gotta say, it feels like I've eaten this stuff somewhere else before, you know?
Well, I have no memory of it.
Oh, I remember now!
At the orphanage!
On Cave Reading Memorial Day!
A foreign...
What was it again?
I forget.
But this tastes like the thing we cooked!
And Nat!
He liked it so much he even tried to take other people's.
Who's Nat?
We mentioned him before.
He's one of our friends from Worth.
Ah!
Nat!
Shiki!
Kiwi!
And Jiduo!
I wonder if everyone's doing all right.
Even if you worry about him, it's not like you'll ever get to see him again, you know?
Still, as long as you're in the Abyss, you Cave Raiders are forever connected.
Rico, if it's weighing on you, why don't you send them a letter again?
That's right!
Let's send them a letter!
This is the sixth layer of the Abyss, after all!
We have to let them know about Team Rico's achievements!
Sure, but can't we do something about the name Team Rico?
It's boring.
Well, we'll use it till we think of something better.
Sometimes you're way too laid back, Rico.
Like whenever we first met, she named me for a dog.
Well, you are kind of like a dog, right?
Here.
All done.
Wow!
Thank you so much, Nanachi!
You sure?
Should you be in the sketch?
Come on!
Like anyone could actually come down here and pursue us.
All right.
The Higa oil to keep bugs and birds away is good to go!
I hope they can handle this bail load.
Mm-hmm.
Shigi once said,
the odds of a mail balloon reaching them from the deeper depths are extremely low.
I wonder if that last mail balloon ever got there.
And that said, is it even possible to make it from this far?
You know, here in the Abyss,
one's mindset has the ability to openly manifest itself.
Now, Reg!
If your fears can take shape and manifest in your body,
then couldn't your wishes also take shape and become reality?
Let's just believe that the first one made it,
and this one is going to reach them as well.
Yeah.
The bird repellent didn't work on those guys, did it?
Don't worry about it.
I bet your mom screwed up plenty of times like that before, too.
Let's hit the sack for the night.
Yeah.
I'll just soak in bed.
The bird repellent didn't work on those guys.
What's going on here?
She's gone!
She's not here!
Krushka's not here!
Even though I was wearing her!
Where is she?
Someone snatched the mail balloon from that bird.
Tracked us without me sensing their consciousness.
Got through Reg's arm trap with ease.
And made a mess of things.
I don't know who we're dealing with or even what it is they want from us.
Iron.
But it isn't blood that's on here.
It's got some kind of mineral.
And I smell some fat mixed in there, too.
Going to the extra trouble of leaving clues behind.
They're taking us for idiots.
Let's get going, then.
We're going to get Prushka back.
No changes in the force field.
Prushka's scent is still there.
Faint, but still present.
This way.
Good doggy.
Hey, guys.
Mania just found something.
Whoa.
Look at this.
Must be the remains of some small animals.
Does this little thing have its butt sewn shut?
Mixed in with the flesh and fat.
There's something else in here.
Is that...
It looks like hair, right?
Can you follow their trail using that?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Oh, no.
No way.
This came from you and Riko, Nanachi.
Oh, my God.
He's right.
Riko's pigtail.
And my tail hairs.
They plucked other spots, too, trying not to be noticeable.
They did whatever they wanted, assaulting us as we slept there unaware.
Damn them.
Irredeemable.
Hey, maybe we should stop and take a moment to regroup.
Let's get going.
We can't let something like this scare us.
Nya!
Baby!
Oh, my God.
Can't believe me?
He was wrong.
His soul's DNA surprised.
He was amber and he was more damaged.
I was not sorry for his wain.
I think his soul was bigger and前.
Footprints
Bipedal
And seems really big
So, is this who we're after?
I can't tell
But we all seem to be headed in the same direction
They're moving upwind
Toward where the scent is stronger
Let's go
This must be it
Well, I've got a hunch we're about to have an encounter
Another structure
Some sort of tower
It almost looks like the carcass of some creature
Hey, you guys
Do you notice anything?
To the top right of the entrance
It's that symbol
The one marked on our picture
What's it mean, Nanaji?
Beats the heck out of me, but
Let's go
We are gonna get our Prushka back
Yeah, Riko, you said it
Luckily, the ground leading to that entrance is pretty level
No need to worry about the streams coming or going
Interesting
All this stuff's new to me
Are you two ready for this?
Nah
We'll at least make a lot of smoke as we make our way there
Counting on you if things go bad
I'll take care of it
Now, you two better get ready for this
Uh-huh
Did you hear that, Nanaji?
Hear what?
Tell me
Nah, but I have no idea where it's coming from
It does kind of sound like a person's voice, though
What's going on?
Riko, someone's watching us right now
I don't know who or what
But let's keep going
Stopping would be dangerous
Are those human body parts?
Hey, is something blocking the smoke?
Is it the force field?
What do you think?
Don't know
I'm not able to see it either
It does look like the force field is interrupted here, though
No idea what it could be
I suppose I'm up now
Okay
I'm about to go through
Thanks for doing this
I know you're easily scared
So, guys, am I inside yet?
What's going on?
Give me an update
Ears
Nails
Jaws
Rips
What could this be?
I know you're like
That's not mereka's
A nightmare
I know you're connected
I know you're not there
You're not there
You're just there
You're not sure you're connected
I know you're connected
You're not there
I know you're not there
I know you're connected
And you're waiting
I know you're together
Get the effect
I know you're stuck
Boom
ہers
You're belongs to people
What are... Who are they?
What... What do you want?
We don't know what it is. Don't be hasty, Reg.
Hadimai, it seems you are cave raiders too. Apologies.
Huh?
Nice to meet you. My name is Machi Kaja. You brought it to us, yes?
Hey, uh, was it you? Did you steal Prushka from us?
Still?
My white whistle! Life reverberating stone? It's called your worst!
Pajibai. Ah, the stone guests, of course. Follow me. Men. Come.
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
Men. Men. Men.
We didn't know it yet. That people could never return from this area and maintain their human form.
Thank you.